https://www.mni.com/site/privacy.html

MNI Ad Tech Stack
Programmatic (MNIx)
MNI Ad Tech Stack
Programmatic (MNIx)
Newsletter Sign Up
YOUR PRIVACY MATTERSEffective Date: February 12, 2020Our mission is to be clear and transparent about how and why we collect and use information and to empower you to control your personal information. You are not our product, you are our customer.When Does this Policy Apply?This Privacy Policy applies when you interact with MNI Targeted Media Inc. (“MNI”), a subsidiary of Meredith Corporation, through our website, and the advertising and marketing services we offer clients (our “Services).What Does it Say?You should read this policy in full, but below are the highlights.What Personal Information Do We Collect about You?Contact Information (name, address, email)Online identifiers (IP address, internal and third party identifiers, advertising identifiers and device information like unique device ID)Internet Activity Information (browsing history, information and website usage data)MOREWhere/How Do We Collect Information About You?From You (when you sign up for our newsletter, or ask us to contact you)From Cookies & Other Tracking Technologies (information stored on your browser, which tell us your browser, device information, IP address, and how you interact with the Services).From OthersOur ClientsService ProvidersData PartnersMOREHow Do We Use Your Information?We use your information for following purposes:To provide marketing services to our Clients, which may include sending emails or delivering their advertisements to youTo analyze your use of our websiteTo protect us and you from fraud and other security issuesMOREWho Do We Share Your Information With?We share your information in the following circumstances:Our clients.With the other companies owned by Meredith Corporation.With our service providers, who use your information on our behalf to help us with the purposes described above.When required by law or as we deem necessary to respond to requests from public authorities, for business transfers or other related purposes.MOREHow Can You Control Our Use of Your Information?We collect and use personal information on behalf our Clients, who are advertisers.Please contact the advertiser you have interacted if you would like them to restrict our use of your information.MOREHow You Can Learn MoreClick here to read our full privacy policyStill can’t find what you’re looking for? Don’t worry, just reach out to us at MNI.privacy@meredith.com and we will get back to you!MORE What Personal Information Do We Collect?When you interact with our Services, we collect the following information:Contact Information: Your name, postal address or email address.Online Identifiers: IP address, advertising ID, unique device ID, and other information about your device, and internal and third party IDs that have been assigned to you.Internet Activity Information: Browsing history, information on how you interact on with advertisements we serve on behalf of our clients.Where/How Do We Collect Information About You?We collect information about you from:You. When you provide your information on our website.Service Providers. We work with service providers who collect information on our behalf in order to provide services to us. We only allow our service providers to use your personal information in connection with the services they provide us.From Cookies & Other Technologies on our Website.What are Cookies & Other Technologies?Cookies. A “cookie” is a tiny file that’s stored on your computer. it contains a unique identifier, as well as the address and other information about the website you are visiting. Cookies help us know who you are when you visit our website. For example, although you may not log-in when you visit our website, we can use cookies to recognize that you have visited our website in the past. We use this information to analyze our website traffic and make design decisions about the information presented on our website.Web Beacons, Pixel Tags and Other Tracking Technologies. web beacons, pixel techs and other “tracking technologies” are small strings of code placed on a web page or in an email or advertisement. These technologies allow your browser to recognize and store certain types of information such as cookies previously set, the time and date that you viewed the page with the beacon and a description of that page.Can You Opt Out?In most cases, yes! Visit our section on your privacy choices for more information on how to opt-out.Data Partners. We work with data partners who provide us contact lists and other consumers, which our clients use in connection with their marketing and advertising campaigns. How Do We Use Your Information?To Contact YouLead generationTo send you emails and other marketing communications from us or our clientsTo deliver a media campaigns on behalf of our clientsTo Analyze and Improve the WebsiteAnalyze, operate and improve our websitePrevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, comply with applicable law and enforce our Terms of Service.Security and Fraud PreventionEnforce our legal rights or comply with the law.We may use your information for any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information, provided we have obtained the required consent. Who Do We Share Your Information With?Our Clients.Other Meredith Companies. MNI shares your personal information with companies owned by the Meredith Corporation, which have their own privacy policies and are not subject to this privacy policy.Service Providers. We engage Service Providers to provide services such as advertising, marketing, email, and cover wrap/packaging. We may share any information we collect about you with these Service Providers and authorize them to collect information from you directly to support the services they provide to us. We do not authorize our Service Providers to share your information with any other third parties.Legal Compliance, Business Transfers, and Other Disclosures. We disclose information about users of our Services when we believe the law requires it, for example, to respond to compulsory process or law enforcement requests, enforce our Terms of Service, or protect the rights, property or safety of users of our Services, the public, Meredith Corporation and the companies it owns, Service Providers, Clients, Data Partners, or any third party. Over time, we may reorganize or transfer various assets and lines of business. We reserve the right to disclose or transfer any information we collect to third parties in connection with any proposed or actual purchase, sale, lease, merger, foreclosure, liquidation, amalgamation or any other type of acquisition, disposal, transfer, conveyance or financing of all or any portion of Meredith or our affiliate. How Can You Control Our Use of Your Information?What Rights Do You Have?Right to Know – You have the right to ask our Clients to tell you what personal information we collect use, disclose and sell about you.Right to Request Deletion - You have the right to ask us our Clients to delete the personal information we collect or maintain about you.Right to be Free From Discrimination – You have the right not to be discriminated against for exercising these rights.Right to Access or Correct Your Information - You have the right to request access to and to edit certain personal information that you have provided to our Clients.While these rights are only legally required in certain jurisdictions, we do our best to honor these rights for all.  If you are in the U.S. and wish to exercise your rights, please contact the advertiser you have interacted with directly.What Other Choices do You Have?Marketing CommunicationsWe send marketing communications on behalf of our Clients. Any opt-out of our client’s communications should be sent through that client.Do Not TrackWe do not currently respond to browser do-not-track signals. Instead, we adhere to the standards set out in this privacy policy and offer the opt-out choices described above. Additional Privacy InformationSecurity, Retention and Storage of Information. We use commercially reasonable procedures to protect the information that we collect. However, we cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.Children’s Privacy. We do not knowingly allow anyone under the age of 16 to provide us with any personal information online. Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any personal information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. If you're under 16, please do not register for the Sites or provide us with any personal information (such as your name, email address or phone number).Location of Your Data. MNI is a U.S. company and your personal information will be transferred to, processed, stored and accessed by us, our Affiliated Companies and Service Providers in the United States and in other jurisdictions where we or they operate, which may not provide you with the same level of privacy protection as you are entitled to in your jurisdiction.EU-U.S. Privacy Shield. Meredith adheres to the principles of the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework (“Privacy Shield Principles”) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union (“EU”) to the United States, and it is in the process of certifying its compliance with the U.S. Department of Commerce. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles will govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit the Privacy Shield website.Meredith is responsible for the processing of personal information it receives under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, or subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Meredith complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers from the EU and EEA, including onward transfer liability provisions.The U.S. Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over Meredith’s compliance with its obligations under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield. In certain situations, Meredith may be required to disclose personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Meredith commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact us at MNI.privacy@meredith.com.If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not resolved your complaint, you may submit your complaint at no cost to you to JAMS, our independent recourse mechanism, at https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield. In the event there are residual complaints that have not been resolved by JAMS, or any other means, you may seek a non-monetary remedy through binding arbitration to be provided to you in accordance with the Privacy Shield Principles.Changes to Our Privacy Policy. Digital technology is rapidly evolving. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy in the future, we'll post the changes here and indicate at the top of the policy the last date on which it was updated. Unless otherwise noted, all changes will be effective when posted. How Can You Learn MoreHow to Contact UsIf you have any questions or concerns about the Meredith Corporation. Privacy Policy or its implementation please contact us via email by clicking here or by writing to:Meredith Corporation1716 Locust StreetDes Moines, Iowa 50309MNI.privacy@meredith.com 1-515-284-3000
Let's talk.
Contact us today.
© Copyright 2020 mni.com, 225 High Ridge Rd. Stamford, CT | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
